Tech will present the result tomorrow. If you
write about Gardner's report which is giving relief of course, then a
cheap mood is visible and
especially on the margins, when I was telling you earlier about
IT, which sector has the
worst performance, Tech has given a
hand in it for margins, yesterday Tech had a
margin of 19.6%, last time it was
18.4%, we are expecting a big margin,
now look here because the top
line is not that good, so due to this the
company seems to be declining, in terms of Rs 325.7 crore with a growth of about 5%,
we are already assuming the growth of 0.6% as compared to Touch or Infosys where we were
expecting a growth of 0.6%, that will
also be seen in constant EI terms,
negative operating average will have an
impact on the margins of the company and
for FY24 we have given guidance of constant EI growth of 68% and
operating margin of 18 to 20%.  We are moving ahead with
hope and again, as
we were saying in the guidance of Infosys,
here this guidance is
of 6 to 8% in constant EIA terms, now we have to
see what the final guidance has come out
because only on the future projections, we will get an
idea about the position of the company, what is its
strength or is there a mood of decline on
this because
for the future, especially
what is the use of the company in the North American market, the biggest
focus will be on the budget, the country of client budget will be
important and on attractions, that is, in the
current environment, attractions of course are
decreasing for all the IT companies, but you should also keep in
mind that now the focus will be on how much hiring is going to happen
because if that reading is done as
Infosys had said, then
you will be seen focusing on utilization, so all the
things right now are dependent on the country, all the
IT sector companies,
you are seeing a cut of 25% now, let's see
how the results come and  How will the reaction be,
but you must focus on IT numbers.